<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dare2Change</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tagline">Decide. Dare. Done.</string>

    <string name="exHead1">Salutation Seal</string>
    <string name="exHead2">Tratak Kriya</string>
    <string name="exHead3">Vrikshasan</string>
    <string name="exHead4">Tadasana</string>
    <string name="exHead5">Natrajasana</string>
    <string name="exHead6">Paschimottasana</string>
    <string name="exHead7">Ustrasana</string>
    <string name="exHead8">Virasana</string>

    <string name="desc1">\'Salutation seal\' is the easiest and most convenient one to do at the time of studies. This pose increases your helps escalating concentration. Just sit cross legged and join your palms together. Keep your spine erect and take deep breaths. Take your eyes off your textbooks and shut them for at least two to five minutes. Rid your mind from all worries and see how this pose can help you improve your focus. You may do this for 15 minutes every day in regular intervals.</string>
    <string name="desc2">Get a little creative and give yourself a break. Take an A4 size sheet and draw a black hole. Stand five feet away from the paper and now concentrate on the hole. You will see all your tensions going away and that black hole absorbing it up. It really works.</string>
    <string name="desc3">Tree pose is a very organic pose to perform. You have to stand tall like a tree to perform this pose and arms by your side. Bend the right leg at the knee, raise the right thigh and bring the sole of the right foot as high up the inside of the left thigh as possible. Balance yourself on the left foot. Now raise both arms over the head keeping the elbow unbent and join your palms. Hold the posture while breathing gently through the nostrils for about 10 complete breaths. Lower the arms and right leg and return to standing position. Repeat the same with opposite leg after few minutes.</string>
    <string name="desc4">This yoga pose is a basic level hatha yoga pose and should be ideally performed on an empty stomach or three to four hours after meals.Tadasana is great for strengthening the legs and improving the overall posture. It helps in making your spine more flexible and firms your buttocks and abdomen. This is a great asana for relieving any kind of pain or relieving tension from the body.</string>
    <string name="desc5">This pose is great for improving blood circulation and gain better endurance. This is a great asana for getting over stress and anxiety and thus clearing your mind of useless thoughts. It is beneficial for enhancing flexibility and helps in strengthening ankles, chest and thighs. It helps in improving metabolism and digestion and thus helps you in shedding extra kilos.</string>
    <string name="desc6">This is one of the most effective yoga concentration exercises. This yoga is very beneficial in relieving stress and calming the mind. If you suffer from digestive issues, this asana may help in treating the problem by stimulating the gall bladder and intestines. It is helpful in strengthening hip and shoulder muscles. This pose is great for energising the body and activating the spinal nerves.</string>
    <string name="desc7">If you are wondering how to improve concentration through yoga, this backward bending asana may actually help. This asana helps you focus better and helps in improving your posture. Camel pose is very effective in stimulating the endocrine glands, activating the nerves and reducing any kind of menstrual discomfort. This pose is effective in taking care of your overall health.</string>
    <string name="desc8">The knees, ankles and toes should touch the ground, i.e a kneeling position. You are required to sit on the heels and place palms on the knees. Keep your spine erect and breath deeply. Now, you have to bring your left foot beside the right knee keeping the sole of the foot flat on the floor. Place your left elbow on the left knee and now rest chin on your left hand. Right hand should rest on the right thigh, properly tuck the toes of the right foot under. The right knee should remain in contact with the floor. The weight has to be transferred onto the right heel. Now, concentrate on a point in front of you, fix it. After fixing your focus, breathing will remain normal. You can stay in the hero pose for as long as you are comfortable. Repeat it on the other side.</string>


</resources>